Most people that look like me, especially black women, we are the most underfunded candidates in
the country, whether it's a city race, county race, state race, or federal race. We never get
the money that our counterparts get. We can look in California specifically at the Senate race with
Barbara Lee. Barbara Lee is not getting the money that Adam Schiff is getting, nor that Katie-
You give me no one names. You give me no one names.
There you go. Nor the money that Katie Porter is getting. When it comes down to it, when you need
to run an election, you've got to get up on TV. You've got to get up on radio. Nowadays,
we do a lot of streaming. You're doing all these things to make sure that you can get your message
across so that voters hear from you. Well, if you don't have the money to get your message across,
especially in a state of the size of California that's close to 60 million people, how is it that
you can even say that you're in the race? The people don't, they're not even able to hear your voice.